//QESTIONS

let questions = [ 
    {
    num: 1,
    question:  "Who does the Bible identify as the first man?",
    answer: "Adam",
    options: [
        "Adam",
        "Eric",
        "Aaron",
        "James",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man"
    },
    {
    num:2 ,
    question:  " Jesus was born in Bethlehem in what type of setting? ",
    answer: " A manger ",
    options: [
        "A manger ",
        " A bunker ",
        "A hospital ",
        " A castle ",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the 3 man"
    },
     {
    num: 3,
    question:  "What was the name of the shepard boy who took down the giant Goliath?",
    answer: "David",
    options: [
        "Paul",
        "David",
        "John",
        "Jesus",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man"
    },
     {
    num:4 ,
    question:  " We all pray to God for different things. What trait did Solomon pray for?",
    answer: " Wisdom",
    options: [
        " Virtue",
        " Wisdom",
        "Riches ",
        " Patience ",
    ], 
    hint: " Adam is the 4 man"
    },
     {
    num:5 ,
    question:  " He refused to be relented; who was tasked with baptizing Jesus? ",
    answer: " John the Baptist ",
    options: [
        " Zaccheus",
        " John the Baptist ",
        " Peter ",
        " Paul ",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first6 man"
    },
     {
    num:6 ,
    question:  "Which of Jesus' disciple betrayed him for 30 pieces of silver? ",
    answer: " Judas",
    options: [
        " Paul ",
        " Judas",
        " Thomas ",
        " Simon ",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man7"
    },
     {
    num: 7 ,
    question:  " The Bible's most popular verse starts 'God so loved the ?'",
    answer: " World",
    options: [
        "World ",
        "Church ",
        "Belivers ",
        " Jews ",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man8"
    },
     {
    num: 8 ,
    question:  " Jonah's disobedience landed him in hot water. What happened to him? ",
    answer: " He was swallowed by a whale.",
    options: [
        " He was thrown into jail. ",
        " He was killed by his brothers.",
        " He was swallowed by a whale.",
        " He was banished to the desert.",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man9"
    },
     {
    num: 9,
    question:  "Jesus went through a period of fasting. How many days and nights did it last? ",
    answer: " 40",
    options: [
        " 25",
        " 7",
        " 14",
        " 40",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man10"
    },
     {
    num: 10,
    question:  "Jesus' earthly father had his own business. What was his career field? ",
    answer: "Capentary ",
    options: [
        "Capentary ",
        "  Teaching",
        "  Electrical",
        " Fishing",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man11"
    },
     {
    num: 11 ,
    question:  "How many books of the Bible bear the name of a woman? ",
    answer: " Two",
    options: [
        " Three",
        " Two ",
        " Five",
        " Eight",
    ],
    hint: " Adam is the first man12"
    }
]
    
//QESTIONS
// let questions =[
//     {
//     num: ,
//     question:  " ",
//     answer: " ",
//     options: [
//         " ",
//         " ",
//         " ",
//         " ",
//     ]
//     },

let index = questions